cakehealth.com 2012-05-13

# Cake Health | Privacy

CakeHealth works on your behalf to download your health finance information at your request to assist you in managing your health-related expenses. In order to help you with these activities and communicate with you, we collect some of your Personal Information. We give you choices so that you can maintain control over your privacy. We never share your Personal Information outside of CakeHealth or for third-party marketing purposes. 

Our services include cakehealth.com and other websites CakeHealth, Inc. (“CakeHealth,” “we”) may create (the “CakeHealth websites”), and any other features, content, or applications we may offer from time to time in connection with the CakeHealth websites (collectively, the “CakeHealth Services”). 

We may revise and update this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued usage of the CakeHealth Services means you accept those changes. 

Confidentiality is a top priority at CakeHealth. We are committed to maintaining the highest level of confidentiality with all of the Personal Information we receive from you. 

Some CakeHealth Services allow you to import information about your medical history (“Health Information”). To use these CakeHealth Services, you must first complete the Health Information Authorization 

At CakeHealth, we are aware of the privacy concerns of those who use the CakeHealth Services. We will not solicit Personal Information from you as you tour our website, though you may provide that information voluntarily. 

When you register for a CakeHealth account (“Register”), we collect information including name, address, email address, and telephone number. We use this information to create and maintain your CakeHealth account. We also use this information to contact you about products and services that we think may interest you. “Personal Information” is data that is unique to an individual, such as a name, address, telephone number, social security number/Tax ID, date of birth (DOB), and health-related information. At times, we may request Personal Information from you through the CakeHealth Services in order to deliver requested materials to you, respond to your questions, or deliver a product or service. We may obtain additional information about you, such as demographic information, from commercially available sources. In no case will we sell, license, or transmit your Personal Information outside of CakeHealth for any reason, unless you authorize us to do so. 

When you Register, we require that you have a user ID and password and designate a security question and associated answer. If you choose to participate in one of the user forums, we will also ask you to choose a nickname. We use that information to grant you access to the services you have selected or to label the answers that you may provide. We also collect an email address so that we may send communications such as order confirmation or information about the status of a return. We may also send or display surveys about our products and services. 

At your request, and after you execute the Health Information Authorization, we will retrieve your Health Information from your health plan in order to provide CakeHealth Services. You have the option of entering additional Personal Information or Health Information into your CakeHealth account to assist you in understanding or tracking your healthcare-related finances. 

If you sign up for the prescription manager tool within your CakeHealth account, we will collect your contact and payment information (including credit or debit card number and expiration date) to facilitate the transaction. 

When you use the CakeHealth Services we may collect information about the pages you view, the links you select or actions you take using the standard information sent by your browser such as IP address, browser type, and the previously visited web page. 

When you subscribe to one of our newsletters we may collect your personal information. 

CakeHealth is not a “covered entity” or a “business associate” under the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 and the regulations promulgated thereunder (“HIPAA”). Thus, HIPAA does not apply to the transmission of Health Information by CakeHealth. 

The CakeHealth Services are intended to be used by adults. As part of the CakeHealth Services, we may collect Personal Information about your children from you. 

While CakeHealth cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information and Health Information under all circumstances, CakeHealth does take reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information and Health Information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration by using industry-recognized security safeguards, coupled with carefully developed security procedures and practices. Whenever we download or transmit sensitive information, such as Health Information, we encrypt that information. Any Personal Information and Health Information that we store is also encrypted to protect against unauthorized access. 

However, please remember that the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, and therefore CakeHealth cannot and does not guarantee that information you provide through the CakeHealth Services may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

You can take steps in your use of the Internet and online services that will help protect your Personal Information and Health Information. 

Use a firewall to prevent unauthorized access to your computer. 

Use a virus-checking program and keep it up-to-date. 

Keep your operating system and programs up-to-date. 

If you share a computer with others, close all active programs and log out before leaving the computer. 

If you use file-sharing programs, be sure to restrict all other folders or directories to “no share.” 

Choose a user ID that is not the same as a government-issued identifier or your birthday or some other date or word that is either easily guessed or could cause harm if someone else learned it. 

Choose a strong password using a combination of letters, numbers, and special characters that are meaningful to you and yet not easily guessed by someone else. Keep your password private. 

Do not trust email requests for Personal Information. On websites, look for the lock symbol which signifies a secure website before supplying Personal Information. If in doubt, ask. 

When using open Internet chat and forum services, do not supply personal or financial information. When using customer-service chat and similar services, do not supply more information than necessary to define your problem. 

Read privacy statements to learn how your information will be collected and used. 

When you use the CakeHealth Services, you agree to the following: 

CakeHealth may deny access to its information systems to anyone at any time, with or without cause. 

CakeHealth reserves the right to access, read, copy, delete, and disclose information on CakeHealth systems and equipment. CakeHealth reserves the right to inspect any and all files stored or transmitted to CakeHealth equipment. 

You shall maintain in strictest confidence and shall not use or disclose any information of CakeHealth or its managed and/or contracted entities, including but not limited to insured, plan, member, client, patient, enrollee, claim or medical information, or any information of CakeHealth’s computing environment. 

The use of a password created by you does not create a right of privacy to you. Passwords are designed to minimize unauthorized access. You shall keep any password created to access the CakeHealth Services strictly confidential. 

If you become aware of or suspect fraudulent activity or any other activity that threatens the security of CakeHealth’s Information Systems, you must immediately report the activity to CakeHealth. 

Occasionally we enter into contracts with third parties who assist us by filling customer orders or providing other services. Such third parties are prohibited from using any of your Personal Information or Health Information for purposes unrelated to the product or service for which they’ve been contracted. Vendors are required to maintain the confidentiality of the Personal Information and/or Health Information we provide to them. 

Additionally, we have business partners that provide products or services, some of which are co-branded. Partner services and websites are clearly identified. When you request any of these products or services, you are permitting us to provide your Personal Information and/or Health Information to the partner to fulfill your request. 

Links to third-party websites, such as those of our business partners and online advertisers, may be available through the CakeHealth Services. Because CakeHealth does not control the information policies or practices of these third parties, you should review their privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use Personal Information and/or Health Information. 

If we sell, merge or transfer any part of CakeHealth with another organization, part of that sale may include your Personal Information. 

We may use sources outside of CakeHealth to supplement the Personal Information you give us. For example, we may validate your address using other sources or we may acquire demographic, household, or other non-public Personal Information. We use this data to help us maintain accuracy and provide you with better products and services. 

CakeHealth, its subsidiaries, and contractors may exchange Personal Information (which may include exchange across country borders) to fulfill your transactions or requests. We may also provide you information about products or services we believe you may be interested in unless you have asked us not to contact you. 

If you choose to send us your questions and comments via email at support@cakehealth.com, we will share your correspondence with our Client Service representatives and those employees or agents most capable of addressing your questions and concerns. We will retain your communication until we have done our very best to provide you with a complete and satisfactory response. Ultimately, we will either discard your communication or, at our discretion, archive it. 

Please note that, unless we expressly advise you otherwise, the email facilities on the CakeHealth Services do not provide a means for completely secure and private communications. Although every attempt will be made to keep your information confidential, from a technical standpoint, there is still a risk. For that reason, please do not use email to communicate information to us that you consider to be confidential. 

The CakeHealth Services are maintained by CakeHealth, Inc., 350 Brannan Street #330, San Francisco, CA, 94107.
